Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive 1989-2004 MSS 191
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IX: America Is Dying Slowly
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Usless, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Video expenses, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Wu-Tang Clan, 1995-1996 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Condoms - America is Dying Slowly, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Flier ad for "America is Dying Slowly" record release party, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Press clippings, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Press clippings, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Promos & Show, [n.d.] (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - America Is Dying Slowly; EastWest Records America, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - America Is Dying Slowly; EastWest Records America, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Series X: Red Hot + Rio
  Red Hot + Rio was released by VERVE ANTILLES in 1996 and is a tribute to the Bossa Nova sound, with a focus on compositions by Antonio Carlos Jobim. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advance from PolyGram Records, Inc., 1995 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Airto / Flora Purim, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Artist agreements, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - "The Bachelor" soundtrack, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Banana Republic - paid bills, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Banana Republic sync, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Banana Republic's "Chinos" television campaign, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Bjork + Eumir Deodato, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bravo Company, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Brazil II, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Brown, Carlinhos, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Budget and reimbursements from PolyGram Records (label) - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Byrne, David, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Cazuza: Som Livre, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Chico Science / Goldie Co Production, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Record labels, 1996 - 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Crystal Waters (Restricted), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - DJ Soul Slinger, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Everything but the Girl, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Everything but the Girl, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Évora, Cesária, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Foreign sales breakdown, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Gil, Gilberto, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Gilberto, Bebel, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Hotoda, Goh, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Incognito, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Invoices (Restricted), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Jobim, Antonio Carlos, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Label agreements, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Licensing, 1996-1998 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Mad Professor, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Mathewman, S., 1996 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Maxwell (Restricted), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Michael, George, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Money Mark, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Monte, Marisa, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - MTV Brasil, 1996-1999 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Nascimento, Milton, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - P.M. Dawn + Flora Purim, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Profit and loss statement, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Promotional CD collaboration with Mossimo and Details magazine, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Publishing, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Red Hot + Rio, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Red Hot 16, 1993-1996 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Royalty statements - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve, 1998 - 2003 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Sakamoto, Ryuichi, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Samples, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Skylab, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Stereolab, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Stereolab, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Sting / Jobim, Antonio Carlos, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Track by track, 1995-2000 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Veloso, Caetano, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Verve Records (Restricted), 1993-2000 (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Video tracking log, bulk 1996 (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Wheeler, Caron, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Wieden & Kennedy - Zima, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Williams, Vanessa (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Williams, Vanessa (Restricted), 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Williams, Vanessa / Prince Charles Remix, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Cardboard ad - Red Hot + Rio, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Fliers - Red Hot + Rio, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - Invitation envelope to Red Hot + Rio event, [n.d.] (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Invitation to Red Hot + Rio event, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Mossimo Music, in collaboration with Details magazine (Promotional), 1997 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Music You Haven't Heard Yet: Vol 2; Antilles Records (Promotional), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 69)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Rio, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 70)
    - Press clippings (English), 1996 - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 71)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1996 - 1997 (Box 12, Folder 72)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles /Verve Records (Promotional), 1996 (Box 12, Folder 73)
    - Sticker ads - Red Hot + Rio, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 74)
    - Sticker buttons - Red Hot + Rio, [n.d.] (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Nova Bossa: Red Hot On Verve; PolyGram Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Red Hot + Rio; Antilles /Verve Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Red Hot + Rio, Japanese edition; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      Audio sound disc
    - Single (2 tracks): "The Boy from Ipanema," Crystal Waters; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Single (4 tracks): "The Boy from Ipanema," Crystal Waters; Antilles / Verve Records, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Series XI: Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin
  Silencio = Muerte: Red Hot + Latin was originally released in 1997 on Jellybean Benitez’ H.O.L.A Recordings. In celebration of the album's ten-year anniversary, it was re-released in 2006 as Red Hot + Latin Redux by Nacional Records, featuring new bonus tracks and remastered tracks from the original release. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advances from H.O.L.A Records (label), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Agreements, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Artist agreements, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Aterciopelados, 1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Budget + Expenses (Restricted), 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Contact information, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Cookman International, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Cost analysis, 1996 - 1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Label agreements, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Latin, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Publishing, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Samples, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Track by track, 1996-1997 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Flier ads - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Postcard ads (big) - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Postcard ads (small) - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Press clippings (English), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1997 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional), 1996 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Café Tacuba and David Byrne, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Cibo Matto, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by Geggy Tah, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records (Promotional) - Autographed by King Changó, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Simon Says, Volume Ten, Summer 1997 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Temporary tattoos - Silencio=Muerte, [n.d.] (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Slides: Album cover, [n.d.] (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin; H.O.L.A Records, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Latin CD liner notes, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Silencio=Muerte: Red Hot + Lain Redux; Nacional Records, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Series XII: Every Nation (from "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute"), 1997
  Every Nation is a song composed by R. Kelly and included in the tribute album "Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute." (Sony, 1997) Various artists contributed to the track, and they were collectively credited as "Red Hot R+B All Stars." (Reference: Amazon.com)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Accounting, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Clearances (Restricted), 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Contracts (Restricted), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Di, Di, Di, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Evans, Faith, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Expenses etc. (Restricted), 1996-2000 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Video tracking log, 1997 - 1998 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute; Sony, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Every Nation; Sony, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Selections from Diana, Princess of Wales - Tribute; Sony, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Series XIII: Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon
  Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon was released in 1998 by Bar/None in North America, Movieplay Portuguesa in Europe, and Trama in Brasil. The album features 40 artists from 11 countries singing in 7 languages, and was created in conjunction with the 1998 World Expo in Lisbon Portugal. A donation of $100,000 was made in Red Hot's name by Imperio Seguradora. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - 98 Expo (paid bills) (Restricted), 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - 98 Expo (paid bills) (Restricted), 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Advance, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Agreements, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Bar/None Records, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Bar/None Records, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Bar/None Records invoices, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Budget (Restricted), 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Budget (Restricted), 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - CD-R containing folders named "LISBOA R.Hot," "Red Hot + lisbon" and more (Box 14, Folder 25)
      CD-R: 650 MB.
    - Contacts (Restricted), 1998 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Grants, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Marketing - to bill, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Miranda, Carmen, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - MuchMusic Network, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - MuchMusic Network, Lisbon TV, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Petty cash report for TV special production, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - PR / Song by song, [n.d.] (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Production budget / expenses, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - To Padell Nadell Fine Weinberger & Company, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Track by track (Restricted), 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Trama Promocoes Artisticas Ltda, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - TV budget, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - TV clip releases, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - TV releases (Restricted), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - TWISTED America Records, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - US $$$, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Press clippings (English), 1999 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Press clippings (Other languages), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Stickers - Onda Sonora (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Stickers - Onda Sonora (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Onda Sonora: Red Hot + Lisbon; Bar/None Records, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Series XIV: Red Hot + Rhapsody
  Red Hot + Rhapsody, a George Gershwin tribute album, was released by Verve/Antilles in 1998. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Agreements (Restricted), 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Artist agreements (Restricted), 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - [Artist information], [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Badalementi, Angelo, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Bills (Restricted), 1994-1999 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Budget / Expenses, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - By George (& Ira): Red Hot on Gershwin, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Contacts, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Dando, Evan (Restricted), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Details - Levis, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Crew passes for "Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody", [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - General ledger, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Invoices, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Liner notes for George Gershwin: Works for Orchestra & for Piano & Orchestra, [n.d.] (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Live event agreements (Restricted), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Live show, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Luscious Jackson (Restricted), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Marketing, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Merchant, Natalie, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Morcheeba (video) - paid bills, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Much Music Network broadcast payment, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - O'Connor, Sinead, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - On Gershwin contract, 1996-1999 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Paid bills (Restricted), 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Paid bills (Restricted), 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Quaye, Finley / Ernest Ranglin, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Rhapsody (contents: Samples, By George, Details Releases & Verve Memos) (Restricted), 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Session book / Jamaica, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Summertime, 1998-2003 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - To do ..., 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - TV budget, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - TV expenses, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - TV invoices (Restricted), 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - TV waivers (Restricted), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Verve - Rhapsody marketing, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - Video shoot / Morcheeba (Restricted), 1998 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Video tracking log, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - Womack, Bobby w/ Automator, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Details magazine, November 1998 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Details Magazine Salutes Red Hot & Rhapsody: Banner, [n.d.] (Oversize 10 West)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Admission pass, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Invitation envelopes, [n.d.] (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Invitation package, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: Invitation pamphlet, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody: VIP thank-you card, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Postcards - Red Hot + Rhapsody, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Press clippings, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Programme: Details Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody, a Benefit for AIDS Relief, c.a. 1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Promotional sampler: Levi's Salutes Red Hot + Rhapsody / The Gershwin Groove, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Promotional sampler: Selections from Red Hot + Rhapsody, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Promotional sampler: Selections from Red Hot + Rhapsody, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Promotional single: "Summertime," Morcheeba featuring Hubert Laws; China Records Ltd, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Promotional single: "Summertime," Morcheeba featuring Hubert Laws; China Records Ltd, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody; Antilles Records (Promotional), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody; Antilles Records (Promotional), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Table tents - Red Hot + Rhapsody, [n.d.] (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsals - Natalie Merchant, Bobby Womack, The Roots, Ernest Ranglin, Sarah Cracknell, Michael Franti, Spearhead (Box 39)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Details Magazine photoshoot - Smoke City, Duncan Sheik, Baaba Maal, Michael Franti, Ernest Ranglin (Box 39)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Details photoshoot + performance - Duncan Sheik, The Roots, Ernest Ranglin, Michael Franti, Baaba Maal (Box 39)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Davina rehearsal, outside photographs of Webster Hall - Sarah Cracknell, The Roots (Box 40)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsal - Duncan Sheik + Mission 12 - Hubert Laws (Box 40)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsals: Bobby [Womack] & Hubert [Laws] - The Roots (Box 41)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Details press conference - Natalie Merchant, Davina, Duncan Sheik, Saint Etienne, Smoke City, Spearhead, others (unidentified) (Box 41)
    - Photographs (black and white) and negatives: Rehearsal + press conference - The Roots, Natalie Merchant, Morcheeba, Sarah Cracknell, Hubert Laws, Duncan Sheik, Michael Franti, Ernest Ranglin (Box 41)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - By George and Ira; PolyGram Records, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Red Hot + Rhapsody; Antilles Records, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Series XV: Optic Nerve: David Wojnarowicz on CD-ROM
  Optic Nerve: David Wojnarowicz on CD-ROM was released by Red Hot Organization in 1999. Optic Nerve was produced by Red Hot Organization and Funny Garbage in conjunction with the New Museum of Contemporary Art's exhibit, Fever: The Art of David Wojnarowicz. The CD-ROM encompasses music, writing, film, painting and performance by Wojnarowicz.
  Optic Nerve was originally available from the New Museum bookstore in New York City. $4 per unit from the sale of each disc was donated to the Hetrick Martin Institute, which Wojnarowicz supported during his lifetime.
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "Postcards from America, X-Rays from Hell: the life and times of David Wojnarowicz", 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Attinello, Paul Gregory, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Invoices, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Optic Nerve, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Wojnarowicz, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Wojnarowicz, David // Marion S., 1991-1994 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - "Angel with a Gun," article on David Wojnarowicz by John Carlin, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Art in America article on Wojnarowicz, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Press clippings, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Press release for readings from "Close to the Knives", 1991 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Optic Nerve; Red Hot Organization, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Series XVI: Red Hot + Indigo
  Red Hot + Indigo, a Duke Ellington tribute, was released by Red Hot Organization in 2000, after an agreement for the album to be released by a record company fell through.
  All About the Blues is a compilation produced for Liz Claiborne, featuring women artists singing the blues.
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "All About the Blues," a Red Hot compilation for Liz Claiborne of legendary ladies singing the blues, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Agreements, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - All About the Blues / Liz Claiborne, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Budget (Restricted), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Budgets/Expenses - Studio recordings (Restricted), 1998 - 2000 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Cinram, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Clearances - Liz [Claiborne] Thanks (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - CMG Worldwide, 1998-2003 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Contacts, [n.d.] (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Ellington estate, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Expenses (Restricted), 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Famous Music, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Invoices: 1.800 Postcards, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Label and artist agreements, 1999-2000 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Les Nubians, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Licensed tracks, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Lizwear / CD Book. Job / 6.29.00 ..., 2000 (Box 16, Folder 47)
      2 CD-Rs, 650 MB
    - Medeski Martin & Wood + guests, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - On Ellington, 1998, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Paid bills (Restricted), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Publishing, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Publishing waivers, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Recording costs (Restricted), 1999 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - RHO - All About the Blues / 9.12.00, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 54)
      CD-R: 650 MB
    - Seliger auction contacts, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Seliger auction winners, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Seliger auction winners, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Terry, Clark, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - To file (Restricted), 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Tortoise, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Track-by-track expenses (Restricted), 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - All About the Blues; Red Hot Organization, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - All About the Blues; Red Hot Organization, [n.d.] (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Postcards - Red Hot + Indigo (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Press clippings, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Press release, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Indigo; Red Hot Organization, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Series XVII: Artists Against AIDS Worldwide - "What's Goin' On"
  What's Going On was released in 2001 by Sony in collaboration with Artists Against AIDS Worldwide (AAAW), featuring remakes of Marvin Gaye's "What's Going On." AAAW was founded by Leigh Blake, co-founder of Red Hot Organization. (Reference: Amazon.com)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - AAAW (Restricted), 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - AAAW 2, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Benefit loan, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Execution releases, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Letter of intent, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Royalties, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Royalties + Expenses, 2001-2002 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Series XVIII: Red Hot + Riot
  Red Hot + Riot, a Fela Kuti tribute, was released by MCA Records in 2002. The album features Femi Kuti, Fela Kuti's son. A companion film, Red Hot + Riot: Encounters with AIDS in Africa, was released by Red Hot Organization. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "Gentleman" / Warner Bros. TV license, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - 1.800 Postcards, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Agreements (Restricted), 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Artist agreements (Restricted), 2000-2003 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.] (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Barclays / MCA Records, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Colomentality, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Contact information, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Contacts, [n.d.] (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Durban contact information, [n.d.] (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Durban expenses (Restricted), 2000 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Durban expenses, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - DVD, 2002 (Box 17, Folder 34)